<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>LUMO Cybersecurity Updates</title><link>https://happybattles.github.io/cybernews-rss/</link><description>Protect your business — call LUMO today at (928) 277-8369.</description><item><title>Source: https://www.zerodayinitiative.com/blog/2025/5/15/pwn2own-berli...</title><link>https://happybattles.github.io/cybernews-rss/</link><guid>https://happybattles.github.io/cybernews-rss/6196139279.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 22:25:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;img src='https://happybattles.github.io/cybernews-rss/6196139279.png' width='400'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Source: https://www.zerodayinitiative.com/blog/2025/5/15/pwn2own-berlin-2025-day-one-results

The Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) held its Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 contest on May 15th. Eleven teams participated, including the first AI attempts. Notable successes include Pumpkin from DEVCORE Research Team who used an integer overflow to escalate privileges on Red Hat Linux and earned $20,000. Chen Le Qi of STAR Labs SG combined a Use-After-Free (UAF) and an integer overflow to escalate to SYSTEM on Windows 11, winning $30,000. The first ever winner of the AI category in Pwn2Own history is Sina Kheirkhah of Summoning Team who successfully exploited Chroma, earning $20,000. However, several teams were unsuccessful and some winners had their awards reduced due to known but unpatched bugs or N-day exploits. Act now to protect your business — call LUMO today at (928) 277-8369.]]&gt;</description><enclosure url="https://happybattles.github.io/cybernews-rss/6196139279.png" length="0" type="image/png" /></item><item>
      <title>Featuring-Call-Exploits-Underway</title>
      <link>https://www.zerodayinitiative.com/blog/2025/5/14/pwn2own-berlin-the-full-schedule</link>
      <description>
        The Pwn2Own Berlin competition is underway, featuring top security researchers testing various systems, including an AI category for the first time. High-value targets include NVIDIA Triton Inference Server, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Microsoft Windows 11, and more. Participants have until May 15th to attempt vulnerability exploits in a bid to win cash prizes and Master of Pwn Points. Act now to protect your business — call LUMO today at (928) 277-8369.
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:46:14 -0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.zerodayinitiative.com/blog/2025/5/14/pwn2own-berlin-the-full-schedule</guid>
    </item>
  </channel></rss>